Stark, Arthur Papers on the President's Emergency Board #219 5934
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arthur Stark Papers on the President's Emergency Board #219
1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Stark, Arthur
5934
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Sources, papers (documents).
Disputes between Railroads represented by The National Carriers Conference Committee & Their Employers represented by certain labor organizations.
3126351
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5014: Railroad Case Files 5030: U.S. Emergency Board No. 179 Exhibits and Related Material 5034: Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5484: Railway Labor Executives' Association Records 5488 B: BRAC Records 5489: Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company Agreements 5728: Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5950: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases 5960: E. Wight Bakke Additional Papers 6066: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6434: E. Wight Bakke Collections
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Sources; Stark, Arthur.
3126351
- Disputes between Railroads represented by The National Carriers Conference Committee & Their Employers represented by certain labor organizations. Exhibits and proceedings.. (Box 1)
  - Dispute Between National Carriers' Conference Committee and their Employees Joint Exhibit #1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dispute Between National Carriers' Conference Committee and their Employees Joint Exhibit #2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 Carmen's Exhibit No. 38 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Carmen's Exhibit No. 37 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Before the President's Emergency Board No. 219 - Exhibits of Transportation Communications International Union (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Before Presidential Emergency Board No. 219 - Presentation of Various Unions, Vol. III (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - History and Current Provisions of Railroad Health and Welfare Plan (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Carmen's Issues Part 1 of 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Analysis of Freight Railroad Operating Expenses and the Role of Labor Costs (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings: Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 493-593) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings: Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 938-1181) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings: Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 650-937) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings: Emergency Board No. 219 (1340-1560) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings: Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 1182-1339) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings: Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 522-649) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Official Transcripts of Proceedings: Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 1-307) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Disputes between Railroads represented by The National Carriers Conference Committee & Their Employers represented by certain labor organizations. Exhibits and proceedings.. (Box 2)
  - Emergency Board No. 219: Statement of International President Richard I. Kilroy (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Board No. 219: Carmen's Rebuttal to Carriers' Presentation on Subcontracting (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Board No. 219: Rebuttal Submission (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Board No. 219: Presentation of Various Unions Volume 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings - Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 1-291) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings - Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 308-521) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings - Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 1799-1973) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings - Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 1561-1798) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - History of Dispute (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Selected Class I Rail Carrier Line Transfers (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Opening Submission of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Cost of Living and Rising Real Wages (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Sham Intra corporate Transfers (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Employee Protections (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Skills, Responsibilities, and Work of Signalmen (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Opening Submission of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Advanced Training (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Presentation of Various Unions Vol. II (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Advanced Training (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Rail Labor's Recommendations (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Appendices to Presentation Vol. I (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Disputes between Railroads represented by The National Carriers Conference Committee & Their Employers represented by certain labor organizations. Exhibits and proceedings.. (Box 3)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Statement of Mac A. Fleming (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Supplement to the Opening Statement (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - CSXT Line Transfers (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits to UTU Submission on Crew Consist Part II (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Attachment to UTU Submission on Wages and Rules (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits to UTU Submission on Crew Consist Part I (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Statement of Regional Signal Maintainer W.A. Barrows (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Statement of Electronic Technician J.E. Havrilla (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Statement of Electronic Signal Specialist C.E. Witte (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Advanced Training (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Statement of V.M. Speakman Jr., President of Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Labor Organizations' Summary of Argument (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Rebuttal Submission of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage Legal Comparisons and the Wage Progression Issue (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Guaranteed Work Arrangement (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Off-Track Vehicle Accident Benefits (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Financial Position of the Railroad Industry (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage Level Comparisons (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Emergency No. 219 - Rebuttal to Carriers' Submission on Management Rights, etc. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Presentation of American Train Dispatchers Association (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Miscellaneous Rebuttal Material (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Rebuttal Statement of International President Richard I. Kilroy (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - UTU Rebuttal to Carrier's Presentation (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Rebuttal Statement of International President Richard I. Kilroy (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Labor Organizations' Summary of Argument (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Norfolk Southern Line Transfers (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Presentation of Carmen's Issues Part 2 of 4 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Presentation of Carmen's Issues Part 3 of 4 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Presentation of Carmen's Issues Part 4 of 4 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Outside Contracting (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Intermodal Competition and Labor Costs (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Historical Wage Comparisons and Current Bargaining Decisions (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Paid Leave (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Expenses Away From Home (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Materiality of Ability-to-Pay in Railroad Bargaining (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Disputes between Railroads represented by The National Carriers Conference Committee & Their Employers represented by certain labor organizations. Reports and exhibits.. (Box 4)
  - Exhibits to UTU Submission on Crew Consist Part III (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Financial Condition and Prospects of the Class I Railroad Industry (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Statement of Richard E. Briggs (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices to Statement of Charles I. Hopkins Jr (Vol. II) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rule Issues (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Job Sharing and Ground Service Wages (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rule Issues, Road/Yard Restrictions (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Issues, Competing for Traffic (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Regional Railroad v. Major Railroads (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Report to President by Emergency Board No. 219 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - National Railway Labor Conference (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Railway Medical Plans (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Comparison of Carrier/Labor Positions (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - GAO: Report to Congress on Health Insurance (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Appendices to Presentation Vol. IV (Appendix G-1 through G-7) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Presidential Emergency Board No. 219 - UTU Submission Health and Welfare Crew Consist (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - UTU Statements to Emergency Board (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Disputes between Railroads represented by The National Carriers Conference Committee & Their Employers represented by certain labor organizations. Reports and exhibits.. (Box 5)
  - The Proposed Contract between United Mine Workers and Pittston Coal Group (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Strike Settlement Agreement (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NYNEX Information Resources Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices O-Q to Rebuttal Statement of Charles I. Hopkins Jr. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices R-T to Rebuttal Statement of Charles I. Hopkins Jr. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices to Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Vol III) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Assignment of Mechanical Work (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Basis of Pay in Road Service (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Statement of Michael H. Walsh (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Statement of Michael H. Walsh (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Listing of Issues with Citations to Carrier and Organization Presentations (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Carrier's Rebuttal (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Contracting out of Service and Intermodal Work (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Contracting Out of Mechanical Work (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Economic and Financial Factors Affecting the Railroad Industry (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Re: Health and Welfare (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Total Compensation Costs and the "Wage Equivalent" Concept (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Additional Attachments to Statement by Thomas Harter and Cynthia Hosay (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Official Transcript of Proceedings - Emergency Board No. 219 (Pages 292-498) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - History of Dispute (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Statement by Richard I. Kilroy (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Rail Labor's Recommendations to Control Health and Welfare Costs (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Carriers' Statement of Position (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Future Economic Impact of Proposals by Rail Labor and the Carriers (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Rail Labor's Statement of Issues in Dispute (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Rebuttal Statement by Thomas R. Harter and Cynthia K. Hosay, Martin E. Segal Company (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Disputes between Railroads represented by The National Carriers Conference Committee & Their Employers represented by certain labor organizations. Reports and exhibits.. (Box 6)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices to D-G to Rebuttal Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Rebuttal Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Including Appendices A-C) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendix U to Rebuttal Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Rebuttal Statement of Joseph W. Shuster (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Rebuttal Statement of Joseph J. Martingale (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Rebuttal Statement of Collette C. Goodman (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Rebuttal Statement of Richard E. Briggs (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Rebuttal Statement of James H. Brennan, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices to Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. Vol. IV (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendix H to Rebuttal Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices I-J to Rebuttal Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices K-N to Rebuttal Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Appendices to Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Statement of Robert E. Upton (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Statement of Joseph J. Martingale (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Statement of Howard R. Veit (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Health and Welfare Issues, Statement of James H. Brennan, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Interdivisional Service (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Employee Protection (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Statement to the Nature of Trailer Train Company Repair Operations (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Carriers' Statement of Position (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wages and Work Rules Issues, Contracting Out and Assignment of Maintenance of Way Work (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Report to Transportation-Communications International Union Vol. I (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Statements of R.E. Swert and J.B. Dagnon (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Carrier Position on the Recommendations of the TCU-NRLC Study Commission (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, All-Union Work Rule (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Incidental Work for Operating Craft Employees (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Report of the Transportation-Communications International Union Study Commission Vol. II (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Wage Levels for Non-Operating Craft Employees (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Study of Pay of Locomotive Engineer Jobs (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Study of the Pay Relationship Between Conductor and Trainman Jobs (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Wage Levels and Pay System (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Job Sharing and Ground Service Wages (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Employee Protection in Line Sales and Other Transactions (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Dispatchers and Yardmasters (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Work Flexibility for Maintenance of Way and Signal Employees (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Emergency Board No. 219 - Wage and Work Rules Issues, Introduction to Carriers' General Wage Case (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Report of the Transportation-Communications International Union and the National Railway Labor Conference Study Commission (8/9/89) (Box 6, Folder 38)